hey y'all how's it going merry Christmas
happy New Year got my
new herf in you can see that right here
herf you know what a herf
is but this is the
herf
coolidor by herf and it comes with these
three trays like this so what I've done
is I
took just to get this thing prepared
it's not even ready yet it comes with
three of these trays like this with
three of these to go in each one I'm
going to show you how they all fit
together you can arrange these however
you
want these slats come out or the
dividers come out and they go into these
slots so however you want to arrange
this
thing some of them you
know just fit right in those SL
lot so I want a big section in here or
whatever small section or I could just
take this out Al together and just leave
it wide open don't have to have these in
there don't have to have these in there
maybe you want a a special you know
certain cigars separated for whatever
reason you want and so you've got your
your little special cigars in here you
can see this is pretty
much two trays deep almost it goes a
little little bit above the edge so it's
not like you could stack two of these
together because another tray this thing
there's two more of these that will fit
on top of each other what you can see
here
is there's a lip you can see this lip
right here and that other tray fits on
top of this form fitted and these things
they've got some nice handles on the
side when you're doing it from the
inside you'll have to grab them in like
this and it just sits down at the bottom
another tray got one right off to the
side here it will just
fit boom it's in there put the other one
on top I could put this this one these
little boxes all in the same tray
whatever I want to do interesting little
point about this too is these are all
these are these come apart these are
these have got little magnets on there
and magnets on the end here these little
dots right there if you can see that
little dot right there and then little
magnets here so then those just snap
back together and I've got my individual
tray for whatever reason you put that in
there so what I've done
is taking these
out I got
my where did I put that oh there it is
so I've already done this
this is you can see I've wiped it down
and I got a lot of dust and things off
of these trays this is a a non- lint you
want something that's not going to leave
lint behind in your trays I took my
distilled water always always use
distilled
water and this is just very damp it is
not dripping wet at all and I'm just
wiping the trays down not to humidify
them but to remove any type of dust or
debris that that could be in there and
you can see what happened to this to
this towel so I definitely got some
stuff off there so I've already wiped
everything down and um like I said um
you can arrange this however you want so
I'm going to reach in here I'm going to
take this one back out so what I'm in
the process of doing right now is I need
to condition this thing to get ready to
put my cigars in there
now this thing is
rated at being able to
hold
cigars that one's in there now I wipe
this down inside outside all the way
around got
everything I'm going to put this tray in
there and I'm going to set that in there
boom right there the top has got a lip
on there too you can see this lip here
lip here and it's going to sit inside
this lip it's got these nice cables on
the side so it won't extend way past
where it
should and then it's got a nice metal
clasp right here you can hear that
that's metal clasp and it's going to sit
down and you're going to lock it it's
got some nice handles right here so you
can pick this thing up
take the clasp off so what I'm going to
do is I think in the metal middle tray
so it's even you know it's in a
centralized location so I'm going to
take this
out and I've got a shallow
disc
dish and I am going to fill it with my
distilled water
now you don't want to be clumsy or
anything and Spills so I would advise
you to fill the tray off to the
side you don't have
to have it totally full or
anything cuz if it evaporates you can
just put some more in there which it
will absorb I should say into the
woods so I've got some water in there
I'm going to put it down here in the
middle
tray put this one on top of
it close the lid lock it and you
know once that's
set this baby is going to stay shut for
at least a week I am also going to send
in there I got I found these little
goes and these are
Bluetooth humid uh humid um hygrometers
and this comes in a pack of them so
little bitty hygrometer well you hook it
up to your phone you can see what what
you can rename it I'll name this one
herf
coolidor and got the batteries in there
you just pull this tab out it's
activated once you hook up to
Bluetooth so then I'm going to stick
this in here off to the side off to the
corner not directly over the top of the
water but over here in the corner I'm
going to lock it back up and like I said
this thing is going to stay shut for at
least a week now on my phone without
having to open this I'll be able to
monitor the humidity and temperature
inside this thing I've got several of
these in other tupp aors I've got so I
got this one hopefully I will be able to
condense into here and get rid of a
couple of my other
Kolors or my tupp aors into this
coolidor this one being it's got the
trays it's very cool I've got trays in
one of my other coolidor or tupp adors
so I want to be able to centralize
everything a little bit more very cool
product it looks great I could you know
I can sit something else on the top it's
got a nice Ridge here this is the herf
coolidor and um I think it's a great
product I'm looking forward to using it
guys Merry Christmas and happy New Year